Hi, in this lesson, we will talk about one mode in Kursor.
It's one of the most powerful features that help you can do big and complex coding task
more easily, and it also was one of the latest feature Kursor was released.
So, when you turn on one mode, Kursor doesn't just start coding right away.
In that it just create a clear step-by-step plan, like to do least for your task, this helps
to understand what's going to happen before any code will be written, and you can save
a lot of tokens.
So, it's especially useful when you ask Kursor to do some some large, like, for example,
you have your dashboard page and application and you want to redesign it, and you just
want to create a plan first about splitting on the steps, and then do it one by one.
For example, you want to connect your application to a new API, and this was some data
in table.
It's a lot of work, and it's better to start with a plan.
So, now let's see how it works.
So, here you can see quickly about the Kursor plan that creates the tablet plan, do some
researches in your code base, and build exactly the specification here.
Okay, let's start with a plan, for example, to quickly switch to the plan mode, you can
use Shift + Stop Combination, and you see it was switched, or you can just click on this
drop-down and choose the plan mode.
You can also click Edit, you can set the model you prefer to work with.
If you want paid plan, you can use any other models, but for example, what else you can edit,
you can also set some key by then, so just see some hot keys for it.
Okay, let's ask some questions, so we have a currency converter application, and we have
our rates hardcoded.
But what if I want to carry it up-to-date, every time I run an application, and I will
ask for source to fetch the latest current rates from an API, so it's complex task because
we need to first find the external API where we can get the current rates, then we need
to build an API call, we need to fetch it, we need to store it somewhere, and set
rates kind of complex task, and I don't run it until it will be executing, I will explain
you how it works under the hood.
So, I could sort of ask you, might ask you some time, some qualifying questions, make sure
you really understand what you mean, so you see, we have some qualification questions,
so which currency exchange rates API would like to use exchange rate API, fixer, let's
say the first one, I don't really did the research about them, but let's just need to
give an example of a plan, when should the rates be fetched, once during initialization
constructor on demand, when you method automatically before each conversation, both initial
and on demand, let's say once during initialization, okay, and the next question should
the fetched rates replace the hardcoded defaults or supplement them, sure, we need to
replace because our hardcoded not actually anymore have to date, so I will answer.
So, then, we sort of will do research of your code waste, to collect all the relevant information
it needs, you see it use the auto source you can, although it on and continue to allow
search and the exchange rate API, and point out the search and web, so it will do the
research of your code waste, to get all the relevant information you need, the file structure,
the import, the existing components and so on, as you see it's the fetchly discount rates
from exchange rate, integrate exchange rate API, okay, it's doing it, so, and after that
it will create the plan for you, this plan is completely stuff what changes should be made
step by step, once the plan is ready, you can review it, edit or comment on it before letting
close or start coding, this will give you a really full control of what's going to happen,
so, let's see what the plan is, so implementation steps, update currency converter, make
the constructor asynchronous, to be able to execute the API, add API keys, fetch rates
from the API and point, keep the code iterate at all back, if API call 1B, and we will
do an error, for example, just to have a good user experience, handle errors gracefully
with strike edge, but, for example, I don't like this app for that rate, because imagine
in a year, the rates will be different and user will get the wrong result, so, we have
ability to edit it, so, idle, first, never use of back rates, and I will mention the line
version, delete it, so, let's continue to review it, file currency converter, just create
a simple method to make, get request, first, response in a struct, conversion rates, what
it did to response, return object, then we can update the example usage, update example,
use await or then, so, let's say, use only a sync, wait, for example, I don't want to use
promises, I show how to use this without API key, the test, only a minute update unit test,
of course, update package, JSON, I have a model, if not present, keep technical details,
a pain point is response format is, from back strategy, you have your updated base currency,
use D, and there are handling traffic, yes, and you see, we have to the list and for
so, when he will build it, he will do it time-by-step, so, we can click build, but we want
to ask it to make some changes to the plan, you see, it's creating an updated version
of a plan, so we can see how it will go on the slide from a plan, okay, nice, you see, we
don't have any more, the file decorates, you'll see it updated, and it also showed a test,
there's a user on the sentiments, yeah, he should also update the user on their sync, yes,
okay, and also, so, I want to click build, I will explain you more about the plans,
so, the nice feature we have, the message query, of course, also support it, it's small,
useful feature, but it's also can be useful, for example, when restore working on really big plan,
it's an all can take 30, 40 seconds to generate it, and you, imagine, and you, for example,
realize you need to change something in this plan, like, you need to change the builds, you need
to get into change the external API, or external tools, et cetera, so you can type your message,
and you can send it, and restore a view, edit, in the, I would say, it will read it in the middle
of a creating plan, and we'll recognize it, and we'll apply the result, so, they will be active,
so the advantage of this weird messages is that you shouldn't wait till the whole plan will be
built, you can modify it on a way, so this is what I like about this feature, so we kind of
interrupt, or sort, like, not, like, interrupted during the making of plan, and give some more
changes, so, I think it can, of course, create build and build this plan, oh, what else you have,
you can view it as a preview, or as a markdown text, you can need to copy paste it, for example,
or what else, oh, yep, this is everything we have in this plan, you can also add some
items manually, like, right here, I know, great, more files, always are in the series, so you can
edit it on a way, you can edit anything right here, so, it's up to you, okay, I hope this lesson
really was useful for you, so you can use a blend mode, it's a best friend, for managing some
complex coding tasks, it will help you see it before coding, we'll save your tokens and keep work
organized, and so, your cooperation with course, sort of will be easier, the nice, you can review
every step, don't delay it to read the plan, because, of course, sort of it will do something wrong,
but you will notice you expected, you will need to update or change it anyway, write some prompts
and etc, so, okay, I'll see you next time, and goodbye.